CARLOS NIETO

carlosn7600@gmail.com | (760) 912-3350 | Victorville, California 92392

Summary -

I am a diligent worker that can work at a fast pace unsupervised. I have experience working in large warehouses and in harsh conditions. I can solve and think problems threw to get results, and do not mind helping other coworkers who may need help. I am an initiative-taking, quick learning, and experienced individual ready to make my next job the best one yet. Currently going to school for Full Stack Development, and after i finish i want to get a certification in CyberSecurity.

- Skills -

- Forklift operation
- Quality inspection
- Troubleshooting
- Material handling
- Hard working and self-motivated
- Work well unsupervised
- Able to lift weight up to 100 lbs.

- Safe worker
- Able to work at fast pace
- Team leader
- Exceptional communication skills
- Creative problem solver
- Tech Savvy
- Bilingual

Experience

Overnight Stocker | Walmart - Victorville, CA | 09/2011 - 09/2012

- Stocked product overnight which included heavy lifting
- Picked products in system that need to be stocked
- Helped with customer service
- Worked alone and unsupervised

Packer, and Sorter/Slam operator | Amazon - Redlands, CA | 07/2013 - 08/2013

- Packaged and labeled items to be shipped out
- Operated slam which ejects wrongfully packaged items
- Fixed packages
- Worked alone at a fast pace.

General Laborer | Construction - City of Los Angeles, CA | 08/2013 - 06/2014

- Demolished and rebuilt homes
- Always remained safe
- Had to lift weights up to 100 lbs
- Worked fast and unsupervised in harsh conditions
- Worked smart to finish jobs.

Production Line Worker | Insource - Victorville, CA | 06/2014 - 09/2017

- Have to lift 50 lbs
- Cases and put them on the production line
- Worked at fast speeds unsupervised
- Helped others if they needed help
- Covered other workers if needed break or time off
- Maintained area clean and safe

Shipping and Receiving Associate | McLane Company - Rancho Cucamonga, CA | 09/2017 - 08/2022

- Offload and load trailers with product
- Receive product in the system
- Check products quality and condition
- Stored products using forklift, or electric jacks
- Selected orders by hand stacking them onto pallets

Education and Training -

University of California, Santa Barbara $\,$ | Santa Barbara, CA | Expected in 03/2023

Full Stack Web Developer: Front And Back-end Development

Goodwill High School | Victorville, CA | 10/2011

High School Diploma